<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Tacit-Tales</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Tacit-Tales</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 16:42:28 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello You</title>
      <link>/post/2018/10/12/hello-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 16:42:28 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018/10/12/hello-you/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ve been found! So I heard. My work-partner for class said someone found a repository I made to collaborate on the homework assignment. I wonder how long they spent googling variations of the term &#34;protocol validation&#34;, maybe not much it&#39;s not all that common...
Not sure if they&#39;re sleuthful enough to find this little blog. Probably not interested! If you do happen on this though, drop me a line, I&#39;d be happy to share thoughts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Echoen</title>
      <link>/post/2018/10/05/echoen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 20:45:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018/10/05/echoen/</guid>
      <description>Life&#39;s full of do&#39;s and don&#39;t&#39;s. That many apostrophes may be among them.
How to catch cache the fleeting thoughts they whisk by like lost time. Who&#39;s the elephant who&#39;s the rider. How much of now is back then? How have previous potentials reduced to now? Where in time do my roots belong?
There are sleeves of me sloughed off and withered from memory, but existing as standing waves in time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Half One Fifth One Half</title>
      <link>/post/2018/09/27/one-half-one-fifth-one-half/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 12:21:58 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018/09/27/one-half-one-fifth-one-half/</guid>
      <description>It has been about four weeks since the start of the period, and the semester. The classes have been alright, although I had to drop the one I was really interested in: Lambda Calculus. Not sure if I&#39;ll ever have a satisfying class on the topics of Lisp and its foundations.
Protocol Validation is alright, it&#39;s got a good approach to the topics covered. Mu-calculus is up my alley, the way of expressing process is simple yet expressive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello Vu</title>
      <link>/post/2018/09/21/hello-vu/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 20:03:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018/09/21/hello-vu/</guid>
      <description>One month ago, on August 20 I landed in the Netherlands to do a Master degree at the VU Amsterdam. It&#39;s been a journey and already I can tell the experience will be well worth living. My flat is filled with 12 students, all of whom seem to be good company. If I recall, 4 are Master students the rest are Bachelors.
My neighbor at +1 is a hoot. He&#39;s an Estonian studying Mathematics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Systems</title>
      <link>/post/2018/06/27/systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 14:30:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018/06/27/systems/</guid>
      <description>It&#39;s difficult to observe a system, especially from inside of it. A system doesn&#39;t exist as a thing-in-itself per-say, but the relationships and interactions between things within the system. Observation of the system is especially difficult the more complex and larger it is, obviously, but to observe a system from within it as a complex actor is nearly impossible. As an actor within a system, conscious of the system, one has knowledge of what it is that is necessarily incomplete: a member cannot encompass the set.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>